(Beverly:)You're an extraordinary woman.
Thank you.
(Penny:)You know, she's
my mother-in-law.
(Penny:)Why can't I bond
with her like that?
(Bernadette:)Amy's with Sheldon
who she loves like a son.
(Bernadette:)You're with her son...
(Bernadette:)who she doesn't.
(Amy:)Do you realize it took me five
years to get a massage from him?
(Beverly:)Oh, well, that still could be
a big step for Sheldon.
(Amy:)Three minutes.
(Amy:)And he used a kitchen timer.
(Amy:)I felt like a soft-boiled egg.
(Penny:)You know, being in a
relationship with Leonard
(Penny:)also comes
with its challenges.
(Sheldon:)Yes.
(Beverly:)Well, what can you do?
(knocking on door)
(Amy(knock on door):)Maybe it's Sheldon,
here to say he's sorry.
(Stuart:)Sheldon says he's sorry.
(Amy:)Bernadette, I'll give you
five dollars to slam the door.
(Stuart:)I would have done
it for three.